Guide to the Archives Union File Part 2, Section 2: Boxes 66-129 1872-1976
Archives Union File Part 2, Section 2: Boxes 66-129
- The Railroad Telegrapher, 1961; Publication (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1961; Publication (Box 115, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.78:no.11 (1961: Nov.)
  - Item 12: The Railroad Telegrapher, 1961; Publication (Box 115, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.78:no.12 (1961: Dec.)
- The Railroad Worker, 1915-1916 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Railroad Worker, 1915; Publication (Box 115, Folder 6)
    Author: American Federation of Railroad Workers
    Notes: v.12:no.10 (1915: Jan.)
  - Item 2: The Railroad Worker, 1915; Publication (Box 115, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.12:no.11 (1915: Feb.)
  - Item 3: The Railroad Worker, 1915; Publication (Box 115, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.12:no.12 (1915: Mar.)
  - Item 4: The Railroad Worker, 1915; Publication (Box 115, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.13:no.1 (1915: Apr.)
  - Item 5: The Railroad Worker, 1915; Publication (Box 115, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.13:no.2 (1915: May)
  - Item 6: The Railroad Worker, 1915; Publication (Box 115, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.13:no.3 (1915: June)
  - Item 7: The Railroad Worker, 1915; Publication (Box 115, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.13:no.4 (1915: July)
  - Item 8: The Railroad Worker, 1915; Publication (Box 115, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.13:no.5 (1915: Aug.)
  - Item 9: The Railroad Worker, 1915; Publication (Box 115, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.13:no.6 (1915: Sept.)
  - Item 10: The Railroad Worker, 1915; Publication (Box 115, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.13:no.7 (1915: Oct.)
  - Item 11: The Railroad Worker, 1915; Publication (Box 115, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.13:no.8 (1915: Nov.)
  - Item 12: The Railroad Worker, 1915; Publication (Box 115, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.13:no.9 (1915: Dec.)
  - Item 13: The Railroad Worker, 1916; Publication (Box 115, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.13:no.10 (1916: Jan.)
  - Item 14: The Railroad Worker, 1916; Publication (Box 115, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.13:no.11 (1916: Feb.)
  - Item 15: The Railroad Worker, 1916; Publication (Box 115, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.13:no.12 (1916: Mar.)
- Railway Clerk Interchange, 1975; Publication (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Railway Clerk Interchange, 1975; Publication (Box 116, Folder 1)
    Author: Brotherhood of Railway, Airline and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Agents
    Notes: v.74:no.1 (1975: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Railway Clerk Interchange, 1975; Publication (Box 116, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.74:no.2 (1975: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Railway Clerk Interchange, 1975; Publication (Box 116, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.74:no.3 (1975: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Railway Clerk Interchange, 1975; Publication (Box 116, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.74:no.4 (1975: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Railway Clerk Interchange, 1975; Publication (Box 116, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.74:no.5 (1975: May)
  - Item 6: Railway Clerk Interchange, 1975; Publication (Box 116, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.74:no.7 (1975: Aug.)
  - Item 7: Railway Clerk Interchange, 1975; Publication (Box 116, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.74:no.8 (1975: Sept.)
  - Item 8: Railway Clerk Interchange, 1975; Publication (Box 116, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.74:no.9 (1975: Oct.)
  - Item 9: Railway Clerk Interchange, 1975; Publication (Box 116, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.74:no.10 (1975: Nov.)
  - Item 10: Railway Clerk Interchange, 1975; Publication (Box 116, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.74:no.11 (1975: Dec.)
- Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1920; Publication (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1920; Publication (Box 116, Folder 2)
    Author: United Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes and Railway Shop Laborers
  - Item 2: The Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1920; Publication (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: The Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1920; Publication (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: The Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1920; Publication (Box 116, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.29:no.4-5 (1920: Apr.-May)
  - Item 5: The Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1920; Publication (Box 116, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.29:no.6 (1920: June)
  - Item 6: The Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1920; Publication (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: The Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1920; Publication (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: The Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1920; Publication (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1920; Publication (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1920; Publication (Box 116, Folder 2)
- Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1921; Publication (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1921; Publication (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1921; Publication (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1921; Publication (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1921; Publication (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1921; Publication (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1921; Publication (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1921; Publication (Box 116, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.30:no.7 (1921: July)
  - Item 8: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1921; Publication (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1921; Publication (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1921; Publication (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1921; Publication (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1921; Publication (Box 116, Folder 3)
- Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1922; Publication (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1922; Publication (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1922; Publication (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1922; Publication (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1922; Publication (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1922; Publication (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1922; Publication (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1922; Publication (Box 116, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.31:no.7 (1922: July)
  - Item 8: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1922; Publication (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1922; Publication (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1922; Publication (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1922; Publication (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1922; Publication (Box 116, Folder 4)
- Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1923; Publication (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1923; Publication (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1923; Publication (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1923; Publication (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1923; Publication (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1923; Publication (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1923; Publication (Box 116, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.32:no.6 (1923: June)
  - Item 7: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1923; Publication (Box 116, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.32:no.7 (1923: July)
  - Item 8: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1923; Publication (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1923; Publication (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1923; Publication (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1923; Publication (Box 116, Folder 5)
- Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1924; Publication (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1924; Publication (Box 116, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.33:no.1 (1924: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1924; Publication (Box 116, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.33:no.2 (1924: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1924; Publication (Box 116, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.33:no.3 (1924: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1924; Publication (Box 116, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.33:no.4 (1924: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1924; Publication (Box 116, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.33:no.5 (1924: May)
  - Item 6: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1924; Publication (Box 116, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.33:no.6 (1924: June)
  - Item 7: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1924; Publication (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1924; Publication (Box 116, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.33:no.8 (1924: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1924; Publication (Box 116, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.33:no.9 (1924: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1924; Publication (Box 116, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.33:no.10 (1924: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1924; Publication (Box 116, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.33:no.11 (1924: Nov.)
  - Item 12: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1924; Publication (Box 116, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.33:no.12 (1924: Dec.)
- Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1925; Publication (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1925; Publication (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1925; Publication (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1925; Publication (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1925; Publication (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1925; Publication (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1925; Publication (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1925; Publication (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1925; Publication (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1925; Publication (Box 116, Folder 7)
    Author: United Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes
  - Item 10: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1925; Publication (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1925; Publication (Box 116, Folder 7)
- Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1926; Publication (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1926; Publication (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1926; Publication (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1926; Publication (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1926; Publication (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1926; Publication (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1926; Publication (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1926; Publication (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1926; Publication (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1926; Publication (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1926; Publication (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1926; Publication (Box 116, Folder 8)
- Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1927; Publication (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1927; Publication (Box 116, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.36:no.1 (1927: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1927; Publication (Box 116, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.36:no.2 (1927: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1927; Publication (Box 116, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.36:no.3 (1927: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1927; Publication (Box 116, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.36:no.4 (1927: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1927; Publication (Box 116, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.36:no.5 (1927: May)
  - Item 6: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1927; Publication (Box 116, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.36:no.6 (1927: June)
  - Item 7: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1927; Publication (Box 116, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.36:no.7 (1927: July)
  - Item 8: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1927; Publication (Box 116, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.36:no.8 (1927: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1927; Publication (Box 116, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.36:no.9 (1927: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1927; Publication (Box 116, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.36:no.10 (1927: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1927; Publication (Box 116, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.36:no.11 (1927: Nov.)
  - Item 12: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1927; Publication (Box 116, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.36:no.12 (1927: Dec.)
- Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1928; Publication (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1928; Publication (Box 116, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.37:no.1 (1928: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1928; Publication (Box 116, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.37:no.2 (1928:Feb.)
  - Item 3: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1928; Publication (Box 116, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.37:no.3 (1928:Mar.)
  - Item 4: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1928; Publication (Box 116, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.37:no.4 (1928: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1928; Publication (Box 116, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.37:no.5 (1928: MAy)
  - Item 6: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1928; Publication (Box 116, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.37:no.7 (1928: July)
  - Item 7: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1928; Publication (Box 116, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.37:no.8 (1928: Aug.)
  - Item 8: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1928; Publication (Box 116, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.37:no.9 (1928: Sept.)
  - Item 9: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1928; Publication (Box 116, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.37:no.10 (1928: Oct.)
  - Item 10: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1928; Publication (Box 116, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.37:no.11 (1928: Nov.)
  - Item 11: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1928; Publication (Box 116, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.37:no.12 (1928: Dec.)
- Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1931; Publication (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1931; Publication (Box 116, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.40:no.1 (1931: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1931; Publication (Box 116, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.40:no.2 (1931: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1931; Publication (Box 116, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.40:no.3 (1931: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1931; Publication (Box 116, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.40:no.4 (1931: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1931; Publication (Box 116, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.40:no.5 (1931: May)
  - Item 6: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1931; Publication (Box 116, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.40:no.6 (1931: June)
  - Item 7: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1931; Publication (Box 116, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.40:no.7 (1931: July)
  - Item 8: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1931; Publication (Box 116, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.40:no.8 (1931: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1931; Publication (Box 116, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.40:no.9 (1931: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1931; Publication (Box 116, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.40:no.10 (1931: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1931; Publication (Box 116, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.40:no.11 (1931: Nov.)
  - Item 12: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1931; Publication (Box 116, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.40:no.12 (1931: Dec.)
- Report of the Committee on Civil and Political Rights, 1963; Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Report of the Committee on Civil and Political Rights, 1963; Publication (Box 117, Folder 1)
    Author: U.S. President's Commission on the Status of Women
    Notes: Oct.
- Report of the Proceedings, 1942-1946 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Report of the Proceedings of the Fifth Biennal Convention, 1946; Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
    Author: Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters
    Notes: And Twenty-First Anniversary Celebration
  - Item 2: Report of the Proceedings of the Fourth Biennal Convention, 1944; Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
    Notes: And Nineteenth Anniversary Celebration
  - Item 3: Report of the Proceedings of the Third Biennal Convention, 1942; Publication (Box 117, Folder 2)
    Notes: And Seventeenth Anniversary Celebration
- Responsibilities of Women in Social Life: a Study, 1968; Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Responsibilities of Women in Social Life: a Study, 1968; Publication (Box 117, Folder 3)
    Author: Angela Zucconi
- Seamen's Journal, 1922-1923 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Seamen's Journal, 1922; Publication (Box 117, Folder 4)
    Author: International Seamen's Union of America
    Notes: v.36:no.1, whole no.1900 (1922: May 1)
  - Item 2: Seamen's Journal, 1922; Publication (Box 117, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.36:no.2, whole no.1901 (1922: June 1)
  - Item 3: Seamen's Journal, 1922; Publication (Box 117, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.36:no.3, whole no.1902 (1922: July 1)
  - Item 4: Seamen's Journal, 1922; Publication (Box 117, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.36:no.4, whole no.1903 (1922: Aug. 1)
  - Item 5: Seamen's Journal, 1922; Publication (Box 117, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.36:no.5, whole no.1904 (1922: Sept. 1)
  - Item 6: Seamen's Journal, 1922; Publication (Box 117, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.36:no.6, whole no.1905 (1922: Oct. 1)
  - Item 7: Seamen's Journal, 1922; Publication (Box 117, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.36:no.7, whole no.1906 (1922: Nov. 1)
  - Item 8: Seamen's Journal, 1922; Publication (Box 117, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.36:no.8, whole no.1907 (1922: Dec. 1)
  - Item 9: Seamen's Journal, 1923; Publication (Box 117, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.37:no.1, whole no.1908 (1923: Jan. 1)
  - Item 10: Seamen's Journal, 1923; Publication (Box 117, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.37:no.2, whole no.1909 (1923: Feb. 1)
  - Item 11: Seamen's Journal, 1923; Publication (Box 117, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.37:no.3, whole no.1910 (1923: Mar. 1)
  - Item 12: Seamen's Journal, 1923; Publication (Box 117, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.37:no.4, whole no.1911 (1923: Apr. 1)
  - Item 13: Seamen's Journal, 1923; Publication (Box 117, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.37:no.5, whole no.1912 (1923: May 1)
  - Item 14: Seamen's Journal, 1923; Publication (Box 117, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.37:no.6, whole no.1913 (1923: June 1)
  - Item 15: Seamen's Journal, 1923; Publication (Box 117, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.37:no.7, whole no.1914 (1923: July 1)
  - Item 16: Seamen's Journal, 1923; Publication (Box 117, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.37:no.8, whole no.1915 (1923: Aug. 1)
  - Item 17: Seamen's Journal, 1923; Publication (Box 117, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.37:no.9, whole no.1916 (1923: Sept. 1)
  - Item 18: Seamen's Journal, 1923; Publication (Box 117, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.37:no.10, whole no.1917 (1923: Oct. 1)
  - Item 19: Seamen's Journal, 1923; Publication (Box 117, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.37:no.11, whole no.1918 (1923: Nov. 1)
  - Item 20: Seamen's Journal, 1923; Publication (Box 117, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.37:no.12, whole no.1919 (1923: Dec. 1)
- Seamen's Journal, 1924-1925 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Seamen's Journal Index, 1924; Publication (Box 117, Folder 5)
    Notes: Index to vol.38: January- Decembner, 1925.
  - Item 2: Seamen's Journal, 1924; Publication (Box 117, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.38:no.1, whole no.1920 (1924: Jan. 1)
  - Item 3: Seamen's Journal, 1924; Publication (Box 117, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.38:no.2, whole no.1921 (1924: Feb. 1)
  - Item 4: Seamen's Journal, 1924; Publication (Box 117, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.38:no.3, whole no.1922 (1924: Mar. 1)
  - Item 5: Seamen's Journal, 1924; Publication (Box 117, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.38:no.4, whole no.1923 (1924: Apr. 1)
  - Item 6: Seamen's Journal, 1924; Publication (Box 117, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.38:no.5, whole no.1924 (1924: May 1)
  - Item 7: Seamen's Journal, 1924; Publication (Box 117, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.38:no.6, whole no.1925 (1924: June 1)
  - Item 8: Seamen's Journal, 1924; Publication (Box 117, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.38:no.7, whole no.1926 (1924: July 1)
  - Item 9: Seamen's Journal, 1924; Publication (Box 117, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.38:no.8, whole no.1927 (1924: Aug. 1)
  - Item 10: Seamen's Journal, 1924; Publication (Box 117, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.38:no.9, whole no.1928 (1924: Sept. 1)
  - Item 11: Seamen's Journal, 1924; Publication (Box 117, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.38:no.10, whole no.1929 (1924: Oct. 1)
  - Item 12: Seamen's Journal, 1924; Publication (Box 117, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.38:no.11, whole no.1930 (1924: Nov. 1)
  - Item 13: Seamen's Journal, 1924; Publication (Box 117, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.38:no.12, whole no.1931 (1924: Dec. 1)
  - Item 14: Seamen's Journal Index, 1925; Publication (Box 117, Folder 5)
    Notes: Index to vol.39: January- Decembner, 1926.
  - Item 15: Seamen's Journal, 1925; Publication (Box 117, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.39:no.1, whole no.1932 (1925: Jan. 1)
  - Item 16: Seamen's Journal, 1925; Publication (Box 117, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.39:no.2, whole no.1933 (1925: Feb. 1)
  - Item 17: Seamen's Journal, 1925; Publication (Box 117, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.39:no.3, whole no.1934 (1925: Mar. 1)
  - Item 18: Seamen's Journal, 1925; Publication (Box 117, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.39:no.4, whole no.1935 (1925: Apr. 1)
  - Item 19: Seamen's Journal, 1925; Publication (Box 117, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.39:no.5, whole no.1936 (1925: May 1)
  - Item 20: Seamen's Journal, 1925; Publication (Box 117, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.39:no.6, whole no.1937 (1925: June 1)
  - Item 21: Seamen's Journal, 1925; Publication (Box 117, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.39:no.7, whole no.1938 (1925: July 1)
  - Item 22: Seamen's Journal, 1925; Publication (Box 117, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.39:no.8, whole no.1939 (1925: Aug. 1)
  - Item 23: Seamen's Journal, 1925; Publication (Box 117, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.39:no.1, whole no.1941 (1925: Oct. 1)
  - Item 24: Seamen's Journal, 1925; Publication (Box 117, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.39:no.1, whole no.1942 (1925: Nov. 1)
  - Item 25: Seamen's Journal, 1925; Publication (Box 117, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.39:no.1, whole no.1943 (1925: Dec. 1)
- Seamen's Journal, 1926-1927 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Seamen's Journal, 1926; Publication (Box 117, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.40:no.1, whole no.1944 (1926: Jan. 1)
  - Item 2: Seamen's Journal, 1926; Publication (Box 117, Folder 6)